avengers= {
    1 : {
        "question" : "What is the first name of Iron Man?",
        "answer" : "Tony"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "Who is called the god of lightning in Avengers?",
        "answer" : "Thor"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "Who carries a shield of American flag theme in Avengers?",
        "answer" : "Captain America"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "Which avenger is green in color?",
        "answer" : "Hulk"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "Which avenger can change it's size?",
        "answer" : "AntMan"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "Which Avenger is red in color and has mind stone?",
        "answer" : "Vision"
    },
    7 : {
        "question" : "Who is the first born child of Odin?",
        "answer" : "Hela"
    },
    8 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of the Thor's axe?",
        "answer" : "Stormbreaker"
    },
    9 : {
        "question" : "What is Captain America's shield made of?",
        "answer" : "Vibranium"
    },
    10 : {
        "question" : "What was the name of the home of Thor?",
        "answer" : "Asgard"
    },
}

bollywood= {
    1 : {
        "question" : "Raj Kapoor was one of the doyens of the Indian film industry. 'Barsaat' was one of the hit movies directed by Raj Kapoor. Who starred opposite Raj Kapoor in the movie?",
        "answer" : "Nargis"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "As of 2020, which is the only Bollywood movie to win 13 Filmfare Awards?",
        "answer" : "Gully Boy"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "The Versatile Bollywood actor Irrfan Khan, who recently passed away, had won National award for which movie?",
        "answer" : "Pan Singh Tomar"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of the National-award winning Bollywood choreographer, who recently passed away?",
        "answer" : "Saroj Khan"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "Which Bollywood actor/actress was recently named in the WEF's Young Global Leaders (YGLs) list?",
        "answer" : "Deepika Padukone"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "Who was known as the King of Bollywood Music?",
        "answer" : "R D Burman"
    },
    7:{
       "question" : "In 'Chaalbaaz' which actress played the double role of separated twin sisters?",
        "answer" : "Sridevi"
    }, 
    8:{
        "question" : "What is Hritik Roshan's debut film?",
        "answer" : "Kaho Na Pyaar Hai"
    },
    9:{
        "question" : "What is Hritik Roshan's debut film?",
        "answer" : "Kaho Na Pyaar Hai"
    },
    10:{
        "question" : "What is Hritik Roshan's debut film?",
        "answer" : "Kaho Na Pyaar Hai"
    }

}


cricket= {
    1 : {
        "question" : "Who was the Indian Captain when India won the Cricket World Cup in 2011?",
        "answer" : "MS Dhoni"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "Who is the highest wicket-taker in the history of Test cricket?",
        "answer" : "Muthiah Muralidharan"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "Against whom Virat Kohli in a World Cup debut became the first Indian to score a century?",
        "answer" : "Bangladesh"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "Who holds the record for the highest number of man of the match awards in one day international matches?",
        "answer" : "Sachin Tendulkar"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "Which batsman has the record of highest individual run in tests?",
        "answer" : "Brian Lara"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "The first bowler to take Hatrick in a World Cup Cricket Match ?",
        "answer" : "Chetan Chauhan"
    },
    7:{
       "question" : "Which Indian captain holds the record for most Test wins?",
        "answer" : "Virat Kohli"
    }, 
    8:{
        "question" : "Who holds the record of highest individual ODI score?",
        "answer" : "Rohit Sharma"
    },
    9:{
        "question" : " The First Player who took the Hat-Trick and then one more Wicket in next ball (4 Ball- 4 Wickets)?",
        "answer" : "Lasith Malinga"
    },
    10:{
        "question" : "Who is the only batsman to have hit a century in each innings of a Test thrice?",
        "answer" : "Sunil Gavaskar"
    }

}


